Previously, on AMC's "The Walking Dead."
《行尸走肉》前情提要
I can't believe he would just take our stuff and go.
不敢相信他會帶我們的東西跑掉
He obviously doesn't wanna be found.
他顯然不想被找到
Yes, he does.
他想的
We came to ask you to join us in fighting the Saviors.
我們來此請求你與我們一同反抗救世軍
People will die, and not just the Saviors.
會死很多人  不僅是救世軍
I offer our friend Daryl asylum.
我可以為友人達里爾提供庇護
He will be safe here.
他在這里很安全
It's time to fight.
是時候反抗了
No...
不
this is something I am not a part of.
我不想參與這事
Gavin, tell your man to stop.
加文  讓你的人住手
Diane.
黛安
Got it.
好的
Good shot.
好箭法
My sister had that dress.
我妹妹有過一條那樣的裙子
Don't think about it.
別想了
Nice.
很好
It's getting to be like clockwork.
越來越有條不紊了
Now, boss?
現在嗎  頭兒
Yes, Jerry.
是的  杰瑞
It looks light.
看上去少了
Perhaps you might look again, Gavin.
也許你該再看看  加文
We've met our obligations.
我們履行了義務
You're right.
沒錯
Doesn't seem like much, but 8, 9, 10.
看上去不怎么多  但  八  九  十
I want his gun.
我想要他的槍
In fact, I don't think this asshole should have a gun ever.
實際上  我覺得就不該給這混蛋配槍
No guns for bad boys.
壞小子不許碰槍
You hit me first, prick.
是你先打的我  混球
What's that?
你說什么
Okay.
好了
Where do we go from here?
這下該如何是好
That's right, Your Majesty.
是啊  陛下
Hand him your weapon, Richard.
把武器給他  理查德
Stand down, idiot.
放下槍  白癡
Suck on it, you little shit.
去死吧  你個孫子
Richard! ?
理查德
Stand down!
住手
Ezekiel, you know I can't have this.
以西結  你知道我不能容忍這種事
We can't have this.
是我們不能容忍這種事
Richard will refrain from attending our future exchanges.
理查德將被禁止參與我們未來的會面
No. No, Ezekiel, you're gonna keep bringing him.
不不  以西結  你得一直把他帶上
'Cause if this doesn't stop,
因為假如這種事繼續發生
if this starts becoming a real problem,
假如這發展成了一個真正的問題
you remember what I said.
你還記得我說過什么吧
He is still batting first on the lineup.
他會是第一個被球棒砸的
Almost did it myself just now.
我自己剛剛差點都動手了
I know it's not his fault, but...
我知道這不是他的錯  但...
this has got to stop.
不能再發生這種事了
So...
所以...
things might need to get a little...
也許以后得...
visceral.
野蠻點
Jared, get the hell up!
杰瑞德  快他媽起來
Let's get the hell out of here.
我們走吧
Can I, um...
我能不能...
Can I have my stick back, please?
我能不能要回我的棍子  麻煩了
Someone gave it to me.
這是別人給我的
Someone who's gone.
這人已經去世了
Gavin, you got to let me turn up this dipshit.
加文  你得讓我把這個傻逼揍一頓
No! No!
不  不行
Just...
你...
read the goddamn room, sensei.
看下氣氛好嗎  大師
Let's go.
走吧
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
最新連載海外影視劇下載 請登陸 www.YYeTs.com 僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
Yeah.
是啊
My sister loved that dress.
總監     送小孩
You were quick with that today.
你今天使棍很靈敏啊
Impressive, Benjamin.
令我刮目相看  本杰明
Told you I'm getting better.
告訴過你  我進步了
You were a trifle too quick.
進步得有點太快了
Just because you now know how to fight
知道如何打架
doesn't mean you should seek one.
不意味著你應該去找茬
Yeah, but it just happened. I wasn't thinking.
發生得太快  我來不及考慮
You have to.
你必須考慮
Every time from this time forward, so you shall.
從現在開始  你都要考慮
Yes?
好嗎
Yes.
好
Richard.
理查德
We shall speak later.
稍后我們得談談
Jerry.
杰瑞
You're sick with this stick, man.
你棍子使得真霸氣  伙計
Hey, uh, do you want to head to the infirmary?
你要去醫務室嗎
No. I'm okay.
不  我沒事
Where'd you go in them trucks?
你們坐卡車去哪了
I need to speak to Daryl alone. That okay?
我得跟達里爾單獨談談  好嗎
Yeah, I'll get you something for that cut.
我幫你找點東西包扎傷口
Yeah.
好
You went to see them, right?
你們去見救世軍了  對吧
Part of your deal?
協議的一部分嗎
What the hell's wrong with you?
你沒毛病吧
You're bleeding.
你流血了
They did that to you.
他們打的
- You know what they are. - I do.
-你知道他們是什么東西  -我知道
You know, if Carol were here,
知道嗎  如果卡蘿爾在這
she saw all that...
如果她看到了
if she knew about Abraham...
如果她知道了亞伯拉罕
and Glenn...
和格倫的事
she'd be leading us right to them,
她會帶我們去找他們
ready to kill them all.
干掉他們所有人
She would.
沒錯
And that's why she left, man.
這也是她離開的原因
I'm practicing.
我在練習
Gonna have to start using these more.
得多用弓箭了
The Saviors are smart enough to know I shouldn't have a gun around them.
救世軍深知不該讓我帶槍在他們附近晃悠
Morgan said you're a bowman.
摩根說你是弩手
Why?
為什么
'Cause we want the same things.
因為我們的目標一致
I need your help.
我需要你的幫助
We need something to move Ezekiel.
我們需要一些事來打動以西結
This is it.
現在就是機會
Alexandria, the Hilltop, and the Kingdom hitting first,
亞歷山大  山頂寨和神之國先下手為強
hitting hard, and then we wipe the Saviors from the Earth.
重創他們  然后從世上抹殺救世軍
Keeping people...
保護人們
dozens and dozens and dozens of good people...
很多很多好人
keeping them safe.
保護他們
They ride this road.
他們從這條路走
If we see cars, it's the Saviors.
有車路過  肯定是救世軍
They've been coming in packs of two or three lately.
最近他們三五人一伙常來
That's why I need you.
所以我需要你
I can't take them alone.
我一個人對付不了
We're gonna hit them with the guns first...
先用槍攻擊他們
and then the Molotovs.
然后用燃燒瓶
Then back to the guns until they're dead.
然后再用槍  直到他們全滅
- Why the fire? - Needs to look bad.
-為什么用火  -要看起來慘烈點
The Saviors who discover what's left...
發現尸骸的救世軍
we want them to be angry.
我們要讓他們震怒
I left a trail from here to the weapons cache I planted,
我留了蹤跡到我做的偽武器庫
to the cabin of that someone Ezekiel cares about.
到以西結在乎的某人住的小屋
Who's that?
誰啊
It's just some loner he met.
不過是他遇見的某個獨行者
Sometimes he brings food.
有時候他會送食物過去
Why don't they live in the Kingdom?
他們為什么不住在神之國
I don't know.
我不知道
She lives out there, she'll die out there.
她住在外面  會死在外面的
It's a woman?
是個女人嗎
What does that matter? She's got more balls than you and me.
這有什么關系  她比我們膽子還大
She's gonna die either way.
反正她都要死的
When the Saviors come and find their buddies dead,
救世軍來了發現他們的人死了以后
if they know their elbow from their asshole
如果他們不蠢
and can follow an obvious spoor,
會追蹤明顯的蹤跡
they're gonna go to the weapons cache and then to the cabin,
他們就會找到武器庫  然后是小屋
and they're gonna attack this woman.
他們會攻擊這個女人
What's her name?
她叫什么
Maybe they kill her, maybe they don't,
也許他們會殺了她  也許殺不了
but it's gonna show Ezekiel what he needs to do.
但這會讓以西結知道該做什么
Her name. What is it?
她名字  叫什么
She's tough. Maybe she'll live.
她很強  也許她能活下來
Say her damn name!
他媽的說名字
Carol.
卡蘿爾
I hoped you didn't know her,
我真希望你不認識她
but I didn't think you'd care,
但我不知道你會在意
'cause you know what needs to happen.
因為你知道必須做什么
- No. - ?Maybe she'll live.
-不行  -也許她能活的
Look, this -- this is how -- this is how this could happen.
聽著  這就是我們的機會
This is how we can get rid of the Saviors,
這就是除掉救世軍的方法
how we all can have a future.
這樣我們都有未來
She's living out there on her own,
她獨自住在野外
- just waiting to die. - ?No!
-只是在等死  -不行
If we don't do anything, a hell of a lot more people are gonna die,
如果我們不做什么  會死更多的人
people who want to live!
想活的人
You stay the hell away from Carol, you hear me?
你給我離卡蘿爾遠點  聽見了嗎
It's them.
他們來了
Look, we can wait for things to go bad,
我們可以等著事情變糟
we lose people...
失去人們
or we can do the hard thing...
或者我們可以咬牙做難事
and choose our fate for ourselves.
選擇自己的命運
No.
不行
Sorry.
對不起
There'll be more.
會有更多人的
Or those --
或者那些人
they're gonna ride back this way later.
過會兒會再從這條路回去
We'll have another chance.
我們還有機會
But we're running out of time.
但時間不多了
If you and your people want to move against the Saviors...
如果你和你的人想反抗救世軍
you need to do it soon, and you need the Kingdom.
就得盡快下手  你們需要神之國
What we have to do requires sacrifice one way or another.
我們要做的事總會有犧牲的
Guys like us...
我們這樣的人
we've already lost so much.
已經失去了太多
You don't know me.
你不了解我
I know...
我知道...
that Carol, living on her own like that...
卡蘿爾  孤身在外生活...
she might as well be dead right now.
她現在可能已經死了
She gets hurt, she dies,
如果她受傷  她死了
if she catches a fever,
她染上風寒
if she's taken out by a walker...
她被行尸殺了...
if she gets hit by lightning --
她被閃電劈中...
anything -- anything happens to her, I'll kill you.
只要她出了一點點事  我就殺了你
I would die for the Kingdom.
我愿意為神之國而死
Why don't you?
那你怎么不去死
Are you a collective, or does one lead?
你們有沒有領頭的人
This.
這位
I'm Rick.
我叫瑞克
We own your lives.
你們的命在我們手里
You want buy them back?
想換回去嗎
Have anything?
你們有什么好東西嗎
Well, you have one of my people.
你們抓了一個我們的人
Gabriel.
加百利
I want to see him first. Then we can talk.
我想先見見他  然后再談
The boat things you took got taken.
你們拿走的船上的東西被別人奪走了
Saw them, so we took the rest.
我們看到了  就拿走了剩下的東西
And we took him.
順便把他也帶了回來
Well, then you know we have nothing
那你就知道我們沒有可以用來
to buy back our lives with.
交換我們性命的東西
That's what you'll have soon -- nothing.
你們也即將一無所有
Because me and my people already belong to that group
因為我和我的人聽命于
who took those supplies from the boat.
那伙奪走船上物資的人
They're called the Saviors.
他們叫救世軍
They own our lives.
我們的命在他們手里
And if you kill us,
如果你們殺了我們
you'll be taking something from them.
就等于奪走了他們的東西
And they will come looking.
他們會來找你們
You only have two options when it comes to the Saviors --
遇上救世軍  你只有兩個選擇
either they kill you or they own you.
被殺或者被他們所支配
But there is a way out.
不過有一個出路
Join us.
加入我們
Join us in fighting them.
加入我們  反抗他們
No.
不
Rosita, don't!
羅西塔  不要
Everybody, stop!
所有人都住手
Just wait!
等等
Let us go, or I will kill her!
放了我們  否則我殺了她
Away from Tamiel now.
立刻放了塔米爾
The Saviors, they --
救世軍  他們...
they have other places, other communities.
他們還有其他地方  其他社區
They have things --
他們有各種東西
food, weapons, vehicles, fuel.
食物  武器  車  燃料
Whatever you want, the Saviors have it.
你們想要什么  救世軍都有
Away from Tamiel.
放了塔米爾
Your words now.
你說吧
If you join us and we beat them together,
如果加入我們  一起打倒他們
you can have much of what's theirs.
你們可以獲得很多他們的東西
Fighting with us, you'll be rewarded,
與我們一起戰斗  你們少不了好處
more than you can imagine.
多到超乎你們的想象
Want something now.
我現在就要
Rick...
瑞克
can do anything.
他無所不能
This group?
這群人
They found me -- here, so far from our home.
他們來這里找到了我  離家那么遠
What do you need?
你想要什么
Just tell us -- we'll get it for you.
告訴我們  我們會幫你弄來的
We'll show you what we can do.
我們會向你們展現出我們的實力
Now.
就現在
Tamiel, Brion...
塔米爾  布里昂
show Rick Up Up Up.
把瑞克帶到"坡頂"
It's okay.
沒事的
Here.
這邊
Sit.
坐吧
Thanks. I'm okay.
謝謝  我沒事
Who are these people?
這些人是誰
New best friends, I guess?
我猜  是你新交的好朋友吧
Where are they taking him?
他們要帶瑞克去哪
All of us, here since the change.
我們所有人  自災變之后
We take. We don't bother.
只拿  不費心
Things grow harder.
但情況變得越來越難
We open cans, sometimes inside's rotten.
有時候我們打開罐頭  發現里面已經腐壞了
Time's passed.
日子一天天過去
Things are changing again.
情況又再次變了
So maybe we change.
或許我們也該變了
Maybe.
或許吧
Need to know you're real with this,
我需要知道你是不是認真的
that you're worth it.
看你是否值得
What did you do?!
你干了什么
Rick!
瑞克
I'm all right.
我沒事
Use them!
利用
You believe us now?!
你現在相信我們了嗎
Just tell us what you want...
告訴我們你想要什么
and we'll get it.
我們幫你弄來
Guns.
槍
A lot.
很多
And then we fight your fight.
拿到后我們會加入你的戰斗
You know we will win?
你確定我們會贏嗎
Oh, I know it.
我當然確定
After, we get half of what's won.
結束后  我們要分一半的戰利品
Oh, you'll get a third.
給你們三分之一
And we're taking back what you just stole from us.
并且把之前從我們這偷的東西還回來
Half.
一半
A third.
三分之一
A third, and we keep what we stole.
三分之一  但不歸還我們偷的東西
Half of the jars, the ones we took.
我們拿走的罐頭  還你們一半
One time, this time.
這次不還價
Yes?
同意嗎
Say yes.
說同意
Yes.
同意
And the guns.
還有槍
Waited by the boat long time.
我們在那艘船邊上等了很久
Want something for it.
想要點補償
So it's this.
所以就這樣
Jars and guns, guns and jars.
罐頭和槍  槍和罐頭
You waited for someone to get the supplies off that boat for you?
你們就等著別人替你們從船上拿出物資嗎
Long time.
等很久了
We take. We don't bother.
我們只拿  不費心
You had that...
里面那個...
thing down there for someone to prove themselves?
那個東西就是為了讓別人證明自己的嗎
No.
不是
His name was Winslow.
他叫溫斯洛
What were you gonna do with Gabriel?
你想對加百利做什么
Go.
走吧
Deal expires.
協議是有期限的
Soon.
很快過期
What's your name?
你叫什么
Jadis.
簡迪斯
We have a deal.
達成協議了
I told Richard no more visits.
我和理查德說了不要再來看我
I am aware.
我知道
Your desire is solitude.
你渴望獨處
That's what I've ordered to be facilitated.
我就是這樣下令的
My men are here clearing the wasted.
我的人是來清理行尸的
The dead are quite inconsiderate when it comes to those who are wanting to be alone.
行尸向來都不顧他人是否想獨處
I thought our efforts would be quiet enough
我以為我們輕手輕腳
to fall beneath your notice.
不會引起你的注意
You're the one who opened the door.
是你打開了門
Tripped my wire.
我的警戒線被碰到了
Thought I caught it in time.
我以為我及時抓住它了呢
Sorry.
抱歉
You hid them well, lady.
您把它們藏得很好  女士
Don't call her "Lady."
不要叫她女士
Ma'am, Ms., missus...
夫人  小姐  太太
You can shut up now.
你可以閉嘴了
Copy.
收到
Goodbye, Your Majesty.
再見  陛下
Hold up.
等等
Cobbler.
水果餡餅
Kevin said you like it.
凱文說你喜歡吃
Just in case you did open the door.
這是以備你開門的
Go.
走吧
Okay.
好了
Jesus took us to the Kingdom.
耶穌帶我們來了神之國
Morgan said you just left.
摩根說你離開了
I was out here.
我在外面的時候
I saw you.
看到了你
Why'd you go?
你為什么要走
I had to.
我必須走
I heard something when I was on watch,
我站崗的時候聽到了動靜
from inside the wall.
是從晲蔬捷ヮ茠
I went into the pantry, one of them jumped me.
我去儲藏室查看  有個人偷襲了我
She was angry because she didn't get the supplies from the boat
她很生氣  因為他們等了那么久
after all the waiting.
最后也沒得到船上的物資
So they made me pack up everything else.
所以他們逼我把余下東西裝好
But she said they were at the boat, so I hoped...
但是她說他們在船附近  所以我希望...
No. You didn't just hope.
不  你不只是希望
You got us here.
你把我們引到了這里
I was beginning to lose faith.
我已經開始要失去信心了
But then I saw you.
但是我看到了你
And you nodded at me.
然后你向我點頭
I mean, just the fact that you knew I didn't leave,
你知道我沒有離開
that you searched and found me,
你搜尋后找到我
that you, seeing these numbers,
你看到這么多人
you seemed so...
你看起來很...
glad.
高興
We will set things right.
我們會糾正這一切的
But things are gonna get very hard before that time.
但是在這以前境況會非常困難
We have to hold on.
我們必須堅持
I will.
我會的
Thank you.
謝謝你
What made you smile?
你為什么笑
What made you so... confident?
什么讓你這么自信
Someone showed me enemies can become friends.
有人向我展示了敵人也可以變為朋友
We shouldn't be going back to Alexandria.
我們不應該回亞歷山大
We need to stay out
我們得留在外面
and look for the guns for this deal.
為協議找槍
Rick is hurt. Aaron is hurt.
瑞克受傷了  亞倫受傷了
I'm more nervous about what Eric will say
我更擔心埃里克看到我的臉
if he sees my face like this again.
又成這樣會怎么說
People back home need food.
家里的人需要食物
Rick wants to bring supplies back and we regroup,
瑞克想帶回補給  然后重整旗鼓
so that's what we're doing.
所以要這樣做
Then I'll go on my own.
那我自己去
We are sticking together, and that's it.
我們要待在一起  就這樣
What is your problem?
你怎么了
We're not looking for a fight right now, Rosita!
我們現在不是要挑起爭端  羅西塔
We're getting ready for one.
我們在為戰斗做準備
It's always a fight, Tara.
戰斗時刻都有  塔拉
I'm not letting anyone get in our way or slow us down.
我不會讓任何人擋我們的路或拖后腿
If we got to stop people from taking from us
阻止別人掠奪我們也好
or we got to take from other people,
從別人那里搶也好
I don't care.
我不在乎
We win.
我們要贏
Grow up.
成熟點吧
Guns.
槍
Soon.
快點
Soon. Or else.
快點  要么免談
Once we get you stitched up,
我們幫你縫好針后
we'll go right back out and find the guns, right?
我們馬上回去找槍  好嗎
That's right.
好的
Do you have any idea where?
你知道去哪找嗎
No, but that's never stopped us before.
不知道  但是這從沒阻止過我們
Tara, you've been out further than any of us.
塔拉  你在外面比我們走得都遠
At least you can tell us where not to look.
至少你能告訴我們別去哪找
Yeah.
好的
Sure thing.
當然
Let's go already.
我們走吧
Hold -- Hold on.
等等
Why are you...? ?
為什么你...
Because we won.
因為我們贏了
And to replace the one you lost.
代替你失去的那個
All right?
好了
Let's go.
我們走
I couldn't lose anyone.
我不能失去任何人
I couldn't lose any of them.
不能失去任何一個
I couldn't lose you.
不能失去你
I couldn't kill them.
我殺不了他們
I could.
我可以殺
I would.
我會殺
If they hurt any of our people --
如果他們傷害我們的人
any more of them -- that's what I would do.
傷害更多的人  我就會這樣做
And there wouldn't be anything left of me after that.
那之后我將不再是以前的我
The Saviors -- did they come?
救世軍  他們來了嗎
Yeah.
是的
Did anyone get hurt?
有人受傷嗎
Is everybody okay?
大家還好嗎
Did the Saviors...
救世軍有沒有...
Is everybody back home okay?
家里的大家還好嗎
Daryl...
達里爾
They came.
他們來了
We got them all.
我們殺光了他們
Made a deal with the rest of them, like Ezekiel.
跟剩下的敵人達成了協議  就像以西結一樣
Everyone's all right.
大家都沒事
We gonna eat or -- or I got to be a king or something
還吃不吃飯了  我得是個國王
to get food around here?
才能在這吃飯嗎
Shut up.
閉嘴
Ezekiel...
以西結
is he okay?
他人好嗎
Yeah, I think he is.
我覺得挺好的
Watch out for yourself, all right?
自己保重  好嗎
Well, you're good with her.
它對你很溫馴
Ezekiel will be impressed.
以西結會印象深刻的
Well, figure any guy that has a pet tiger
我想養老虎當寵物的人
can't be that bad.
不會壞到哪去
He's okay by Carol.
卡蘿爾覺得他挺好
Yeah, I found her, out in that little house.
我找到她了  在外面那座小屋子里
Look, what I said...
我當時說的話
when I said she just...
我說她
went away...
離開了
it's what she told me to do.
是她讓我說的
No, I get it.
我懂
We need the Kingdom.
我們需要神之國
You got to make that happen.
你要促成合作
I'm sorry.
抱歉
I mean, I -- I really am, but, uh...
我真的很抱歉  但是
it can't be me.
不能是我
Look, whatever it is you're holding on to...
聽著  你所堅持的東西
it's already gone, man.
早就沒了
Wake the hell up.
醒醒吧
You're the same as me, Daryl.
你和我一樣  達里爾
You don't know shit about me.
你對我毫不了解
No, I do.
不  我了解
'Cause you didn't tell Carol what happened.
因為你沒告訴卡蘿爾發生了什么
You didn't, 'cause she'd be here otherwise.
你沒有  不然她會來這里的
And I'm glad for that.
我對此很高興
See, we're all holding on to something.
我們都在堅持著一些東西
I'm going back to Hilltop in the morning
我早上回山頂寨
and getting ready.
去做準備